How have you been?
元気してた?
It's cute again.
かわいくなったね、また
That's amazing.
すごいね
The style is nice too.
スタイルも 良くて
Looks like a penguin.
ペンギンみたい
Did you play penguin?
ペンギンしたの?
It's not a penguin.
ペンギンじゃない
Have you had sex recently?
最近イッチした?
I haven't.
してない
You don't.
しないだもんね
It's private.
プライベートだね
I'm taking pictures of the room, so let's go together.
部屋を撮ってるから 一緒に行こう
cute!
かわいい!
So cute!
めちゃくちゃかわいい!
J K?
I love JK.
JK大好きなんだよね
I can't stand it.
たまんないな
Smells good!
いい匂い!
It's full of scent.
匂いっぱいかかして
A young smell.
若い匂いが
I can't stand it.
たまんないよ
I was so excited.
めっちゃ興奮しちゃった
It's short and cute.
下短くてかわいいね
You're tall.
背高いよね
Take this off.
これ脱いで
It's model 3.
モデル3じゃん
She's a model JK.
モデルJKだね
My voice came out.
声出ちゃったね
cute!
かわいい!
I feel it.
感じるんだね
It smells naughty.
エッチな匂いするよ
Are you wet?
濡れてる?
That's naughty.
エッチだね
Is it rich?
コクしてるの?
It's rich, isn't it?
コクしてるでしょ
Because there's no reason.
わけないから
It's round.
丸めだよ
I got it so wet.
こんなに濡らしちゃって
That's naughty.
エ ッチだね
Surprised
びっく
Did you do it?
り した?
I was surprised.
びっくりしました
how was it?
どうだった?
I was really surprised.
すごくびっくりしました
You look happy.
嬉しそうだね
Were you happy?
嬉しかった?
I was surprised.
びっくりした
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
fine?
元気?
fine.
元気
Have you been anywhere recently?
最近何か どっか行った?
Where did you go?
どっか行ったの?
What did you see?
何見たの?
I saw Minions.
ミニオン見ました
That's right.
そうなんだ
Like, friends.
いいね、友達と
I'm going with a friend.
友達と行きます
I'm still a student, after all.
まだね、学生だもんね
Are you going after school?
放課後行くの?
The two of us will go together on our day off.
お休みの日に 2人で行きます
That's right.
そうなんだ
boy?
男の子?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Is school fun?
学校は楽しい?
It's so much fun.
すごい楽しいです
fun?
楽 しい?
How old are you now?
今いくつ?
I recently turned 17 years old.
最近17歳になりました
Congratulations.
お めでとう
thank you.
ありがとうございます
recently?
最近?
birthday?
誕生日?
It's my birthday.
きました、誕生日
Did we meet to congratulate you?
おめでとう会した?
I ate cake for my birthday and went out to university.
お誕生日にケーキ食べたりして、 お出かけで ユニバー行き
I did.
ました
Did you go to uni?
ユ ニバー行った?
I love minions.
ミニオン好きだね
I like minions.
ミニオン好きです
it is?
それは?
With a boy?
男の子と?
I'm going with my family.
家族で行きます
You're going back to school, right?
学校で戻るでしょ?
Are you two here?
ここが二人だの?
To my senior?
先輩に?
What was that said?
それ、なんて言われた?
That's why I think.
だからみたいな
It's like, let's go out.
付 き合おうよみたいな
What's your reply?
返事は?
I haven't told you yet, and I'm worried.
まだ言ってなくて、 悩んでるな
I'm worried.
悩んでるんだ
why?
なんで?
What do you think?
どうなの?
Is it subtle?
微妙なの?
I don't really want it.
あんまり欲しいと思わない
Don't you want to have sex with your boyfriend?
彼氏とエッチしたくないの?
I want to do it just a little bit.
少しだけしたい
I see.
そうか
Would you like to have sex?
エッチしたりない?
Or not?
したりない?
Like.
みたいな
It's lewd.
すけべだもんね
It's actually lewd.
本当はすけべだもんね
Just a little bit about that
ちょっとあの
...
copper?
どう?
I'm on board.
乗 り込んです
Do you want some?
少ししたいの?
Is it just a little bit?
少しだけなの?
TRUE?
本当?
It's erotic.
エロいもんね
Do you know?
知ってる?
I know.
知ってる
I'm making you a woman.
女にしてる
Aren't you a woman?
女にしてないの?
But you know this.
でも知ってるんだね、これ
Because it's literally written
文字文字しちゃってるから
hey.
ね
Is that so?
そう なの?
My ears are vibrating.
耳振動してるよ
You look nice.
いい表情するね
tickles.
くすぐったい
Are you ticklish?
くすぐったいの?
Isn't it just the hair that tickles?
くすぐったいのって、結構髪一人じゃない?
It feels good.
気持ちいいのと
It's so boring here.
たまんないね、ここ
ERROR
なんていうのか知ってる?
Futon too.
布団も
The futon too.
布団もだね
But, when it comes to boarding, it's definitely there.
でもね、乗り込む回では、 絶対いるよ
Young women turn into women with these pumps.
若い女はこのパンプで、 女 にしてるんだよ
i don't know?
知らない?
It doesn't hit the part that feels the best.
一番気持ちいいとこ当たってないね
I can feel your heart.
心臓が伝わるよ
Where it feels good.
気 持ちいいとこに
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
It's above.
上だよ
liquid.
液体が
There's liquid on it now.
液体が今ついてたよ